streamingvideoprovider.com 2019-07-28

# Privacy Policy - StreamingVideoProvider

Last updated:19/05/2018

TeddySoft Ltd. and its affiliates (“ **StreamingVideoProvider** ” or “ **we** ”) want you to be familiar with the information we collect about users of our websites, how we use and share that information, and the choices you have regarding the information you provide. This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) describes our practices with respect to information collected through our website located at [https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com//](https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com/) and other StreamingVideoProvider websites where this Privacy Policy is made available (“collectively, the “ **Site** ”).

This Privacy Policy does not address information that may be collected through services offered by StreamingVideoProvider (the “ **StreamingVideoProvider Services** ”), including those aspects of StreamingVideoProvider Services that are accessible via this Site, including the Video Panel, support pages, and documentation. For more information about information collected through StreamingVideoProvider Services, please see our StreamingVideoProvider Services Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, the policies referenced in this Privacy Policy, and our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com/terms.html). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, the policies referenced in this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, do not use the Site. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or our privacy practices generally, please contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).

### Contents of the Privacy Policy:

  * Information We May Collect
  * How We May Use Your Information
  * How Your Information May Be Shared
  * International Data Transfers
  * Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices
  * User Rights
  * Additional Notice for Certain European Residents
  * Additional Notice for Canadian Residents
  * Privacy Shield Notice
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * How to Contact Us

* * *

### Information We May Collect

We may collect information from or about you, such as:

  * Personal information that you voluntarily provide, including name, address, and email address.
  * Communication preferences.
  * Unique IDs such as IP address and device IDs.
  * Site-viewing activity, such as pages visited, videos watched, duration of sessions and search terms.
  * Referring domain, destination domain and destination path.
  * Geolocation data.
  * Non-sensitive text entered, and mouse movements.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may also combine information you provide to us, either via our Site or via another means (such as at a trade show) with publicly-available information, such as your organization’s name.

 **Information Collected by Automated Means**. We may collect certain information about you by automated means, such as your MAC address, IP address, computer type, screen resolution, OS version, and browser type and version. This information is collected by most websites and is used to optimize your experience on the Site.

 **Job Applicants** : You may voluntarily provide data about yourself in connection with a job application. Such provision of data is subject to the privacy policy of the third-party platform you use to submit your application. You will have the opportunity to review that privacy policy before providing the data.

 **Cookies and other tracking technologies.** We and our third-party service providers may use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about you, such as personal information, information about the devices you use to access the Site and your interactions with the Site. For more information about the use of cookies on the Site, please review our Cookies Policy.

We may also use web beacons on our Site and in email communications. Web beacons, also known as clear GIFs or single-pixel GIFs, are small image files that we, or our third-party service providers, place on our Site and in emails. Alongside cookies, web beacons allow us to accurately count the number of unique users who have visited a specific page on the Site, or opened or acted upon an email. This information allows us to measure the performance of our Site and our email campaigns.

 **Advertising on Third-Party Websites and Ad Networks**. We partner with third parties to manage our advertising on the Site and third-party websites, which may include serving or tracking advertisements on or relating to the Site. Our third-party service providers may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on the Site and third-party sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. The privacy policies of those third parties will govern your interactions with such third-party websites or ad networks. If you do not want this information used by third parties for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if you are located in the European Union, click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Following these processes will opt you out of receiving StreamingVideoProvider ads that are targeted to you. You may, however, continue to receive generic ads that are targeted to the general public.

 **Log Files**. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on the Site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. Your IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to the device you are using by your ISP and, in many cases, IP addresses are shared by multiple people or computers and may be dynamically generated (meaning they change over time). This number is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you use the Site, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) you visited. We may combine this automatically-collected log information with other information we collect from you. We do this to improve the functionality of the Site.

 **Analytics**. We use third-party analytics provided by Google Analytics. For information on how Google Analytics collects and processes information about you and information on how to opt out from Google’s collection of information from you, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

 **Do Not Track**. The Site does not recognize a “do not track” setting (or similar mechanism) from your browser to indicate that you do not wish to be tracked or to receive interest-based ads.

 **Security**. The security of personal information that StreamingVideoProvider collects from Site users is of great importance to StreamingVideoProvider. We use organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect personal information under our control. No data transmission over the Internet or data storage system, however, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. When you submit personal information via a lead form on the Site (such as name, phone number, and email address), we encrypt the transmission of that information. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).

Back to top

* * *

### How We May Use Your Information

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may use the information collected about you for the following purposes or in the following ways:

  * To communicate with you and to inform you of products, programs and services.
  * To fulfill your requests and respond to your inquiries, such as to send a requested white paper.
  * To send you important information regarding the Site, including changes to Site terms, conditions and policies. This information is important, so you may not opt out of receiving it.
  * To allow you to voluntarily participate in contests, surveys or promotions (collectively, “ **Promotions** ”). If you participate in a Promotion, we may request certain personal information, such as your email address. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion, because the rules for each Promotion may contain additional information about our use of personal information that you provide in connection with the Promotion. To the extent that the Promotion’s rules conflict with this Privacy Policy regarding the treatment of personal information, the Promotion’s rules will control.
  * For our internal business purposes, such as for data analysis (including through automated systems and machine learning), benchmarking, reporting, audits, developing new products, enhancing our Site, improving StreamingVideoProvider Services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns.
  * To protect the security and integrity of our Site, and to prevent and to investigate fraud and other misuses.
  * In an anonymous (or pseudonymous or de-identified), aggregated manner.
  * In combination with other information, collected online and offline, including information from third-party sources, to help us update, expand and analyze our records, identify prospective customers and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * To comply with applicable legal or regulatory requirements and our policies, and to protect against criminal activity, claims and other liabilities.
  * In any other ways, with your consent or as permitted under applicable law.

Back to top

* * *

### How Your Information May Be Shared

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may share personal information as follows:

  * With any of our current and future corporate subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * With our third-party service providers, agents, vendors and other third parties we use to support the Site and our business. These parties include, but are not limited to, third parties providing us with services such as website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, analytics and email delivery services. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * With third parties (including third-party event sponsors) to allow them to contact you regarding products, programs, services and promotions that they believe may be of interest to you.
  * With third parties for marketing, advertising, Promotions, contests or other similar purposes. If required by applicable law, we will share such data for advertising and marketing purposes only in an aggregate, anonymous and de-identified manner.
  * With third-party sponsors of Promotions (irrespective of whether such Promotions are hosted by us), or otherwise in accordance with the rules applicable to such Promotion. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion in which you participate, because they may contain additional important information about a sponsor’s own information collection practices.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, proceeding or reorganization involving the business activities for which the information is maintained. In the event that ownership of StreamingVideoProvider or its business were to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your personal information may be shared. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, change in use of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding such change in use of your personal information.
  * As we believe necessary: under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; to comply with any law or directive, judicial or administrative order, legal process or investigation, warrant, subpoena, law enforcement or national security investigation or as otherwise required or authorized by law; to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including outside your country of residence; to enforce our policies, terms and conditions;  to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and  to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

 **Forums**. We may enable you to post information to certain parts of the Site (collectively, the **“Forums”** ). Please note that any information you disclose through any Forum will be publicly available. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose personal information, or any other information, via any Forum. **We are not responsible for the use of any personal information you disclose through any Forum.** To request removal of your personal information from a Forum, contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). We will let you know if we are not able to remove your personal information.

 **Third-Party Sites and the Site**. We provide links to other websites on this Site as a convenience for our users. We may also inform users about third-party services or applications that can be used in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services, including services from companies associated with StreamingVideoProvider’s partners program (as further described on the Site). This Privacy Policy does not cover, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, or of other websites, applications or services operated by such third parties. Your activities with, including your provision of personal information to, any such third parties or such third parties’ websites, applications or services will be governed by the privacy policy of such third parties. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked website by StreamingVideoProvider. **We are not responsible for the use of any personal information you disclose to or through our customers or partners or third-party sites, applications or services.**

 **Social Media Features**.  Our Site includes social media features, such as LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, and Google Plus. These features may collect information about you including, for example, your IP address and which pages you visit on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the social media feature.

 **Cross-Device Tracking**. When you use your mobile device to interact with the Site, we may receive information about your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We and our service providers and third parties we collaborate with, including ad networks, may use cross-device/cross-context tracking. For example, you might use multiple browsers on a single device, or use various devices (such as desktops, smartphones and tablets), which can result in your having multiple accounts or profiles across these various contexts and devices. Cross-device/cross-context technology may be used to connect these various accounts or profiles and the corresponding data from the different contexts and devices.

Back to top

* * *

### International Data Transfers

The Site, and the features and functionality of the Site, may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world, including the United States and other countries. Therefore, personal information about users of the Site may be transferred, processed and stored outside the country where you access the Site, including to countries where the level of data protection may not be deemed adequate by the local legal or regulatory authority in the country of origin of the data. By using the Site, you consent to this transfer. We will protect the privacy and security of personal information we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy, regardless of where it is processed or stored.

 **European Residents** :  If you are a resident of the European Union (the “ **EU** ”), the European Economic Area or Switzerland, please see our Additional Privacy Notice for Certain European Residents and our Privacy Shield Notice below.

Back to top

* * *

### Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices

 **Opt-Out**. If you no longer wish to receive marketing-related emails from us, or you prefer that we not share personal information about you in the future with our affiliates and/or with third parties, you may opt out by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the latest such message you have received or by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). Please specify whether you are opting out of receiving messages from us or from us sharing your information with our affiliates and third parties.

We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. If you opt out as described above, we will not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties with whom your personal information has already been shared. If you wish to cease receiving marketing-related emails from such third parties, please contact them directly.

 **Retention Period**. To the extent permitted by applicable law, StreamingVideoProvider will retain personal information about you for the period of time appropriate for us to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or enforce our agreements, whichever is longer.

 **Use of the Site by Children**. The Site is not directed to children under the age of 16 (who reside in the EU, the European Economic Area or Switzerland) and children under the age of 13 (who reside in the United States). Children under the applicable minimum age should not provide personal information through the Site. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).

Back to top

* * *

### User Rights

You may request, and we will provide you with, information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may request access to, or correction or deletion of your personal information, by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

Back to top

* * *

### Additional Notice for Certain European Residents

 **The following Additional Notice applies only to residents of the European Union, the European Economic Area and Switzerland who visit the Site.**

 **Personal Data and Processing**.  For the purposes of this Additional Notice:

“ ** _Personal Data_** ” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of such natural person. 

“ ** _Processing_** ” means any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

 **Purposes and Legal Bases for Processing Personal Data**. StreamingVideoProvider processes data for the purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy, including providing the Site and other services to users as explained in the How We May Use Your Information and How Your Information Is Shared sections.

Our lawful bases for the Processing of Personal Data are: (i) consent and/or (ii) any other applicable lawful bases, such as our legitimate interest in engaging in commerce, offering products and services of value to the users of the Site, preventing fraud, ensuring information and network security, direct marketing and complying with industry practices.

 **Compelled Disclosures**.  StreamingVideoProvider may be required to disclose Personal Data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including disclosures necessary to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or pursuant to judicial orders. 

 **Additional Rights for European Residents.** As a resident of the EU or a country following substantially-similar legislation regarding the protection of Personal Data, you may have one or more of the following additional rights available to you:

 ** _Access_**. To request a copy of the Personal Data we have collected about you by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).

 ** _Rectification & Erasure_**. To request that we correct or delete any Personal Data about you that is incomplete, incorrect, unnecessary or outdated.

 ** _Objection_**. To object, at any time, to Personal Data about you being Processed for direct marketing purposes.

 ** _Restriction of Processing_**. To request restriction of Processing of Personal Data about you for certain reasons, such as, if you consider Personal Data about you collected by us to be inaccurate or if you have objected to the Processing in accordance with your rights under Data Protection Laws and Regulations.

 ** _Data Portability_**. To request and receive the Personal Data we have collected about you in a commonly used and machine-readable form.

 ** _Right to Withdraw Consent_**. If Personal Data about you is Processed solely based on your consent and not for any other lawful basis, to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of our Processing based on such consent before it was withdrawn, including Processing related to existing contracts for StreamingVideoProvider Services.

 ** _Right to Lodge a Complaint with a DPA_**. If you believe our Processing of Personal Data about you is inconsistent with the applicable data protection laws, to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory data protection authority (“ **DPA** ”).

To exercise any of the above-listed rights (with the exception of the right to lodge a complaint with a DPA, which you may do directly to a DPA), please contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). We will process any requests in accordance with applicable law and within a reasonable period of time. We may need to verify your identity before processing your request.

Back to top

* * *

### Additional Notice for Canadian Residents

 **Canadian residents may have additional rights under Canadian law. Please see the information provided by the**[ **Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada**](https://www.priv.gc.ca/en/about-the-opc/publications/guide_ind/) **for additional details.**

You, and we, confirm that it is our wish that this Privacy Policy and all other related policies be drawn up in English. _Vous reconnaissent avoir exigé la rédaction en anglais du présent document ainsi que tous les documents qui s'y rattachent._

Back to top

* * *

### Privacy Shield Notice

 **EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Notice.**  We have certified our compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield (collectively, the “ **Privacy Shield Framework** ”) with respect to the Personal Data of users of the Site who are residents of the European Union (“ **EU** ”), European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”) and Switzerland that we receive and process through the Site. We certify that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement (the “ **Privacy Shield Principles** ”) for Personal Data of users of the Site in the countries participating in the Privacy Shield Framework. We are responsible for the processing of personal data we receive under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfer to a third party agent, and may be liable for onward transfers in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles. Our certification is available [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). We may also process Personal Data relating to individuals in Europe via other compliance mechanisms, including use of the European Union Standard Contractual Clauses.

 **Questions and Complaints**.  If you are a resident of a country participating in the Privacy Shield Framework, you may direct any questions or complaints concerning our Privacy Shield compliance to our Privacy Shield and Data Protection Contact listed below. We will work with you to resolve your issue.  

If you have not received timely response to your concern relating to data processed under the Privacy Shield Framework, or we have not addressed your concern satisfactorily, you may contact our U.S.-based dispute resolution provider, at no cost to you, at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. If neither StreamingVideoProvider nor our independent dispute resolution provider resolves your complaint, you may have the right to invoke binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield panel. However, prior to initiating such arbitration, a resident of a country participating in the Privacy Shield Framework must first: (1) contact us and afford us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2) seek assistance from our designated independent dispute resolution provider; and (3) contact the U.S. Department of Commerce (either directly or through a European DPA) and afford the Department of Commerce time to attempt to resolve the issue. If a resident invokes binding arbitration, each party shall be responsible for its own attorney’s fees. Pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, the arbitrator(s) may impose only individual-specific, non-monetary, equitable relief necessary to remedy any violation of the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to the resident.

 **U.S. Federal Trade Commission Enforcement**. StreamingVideoProvider’s commitments under the Privacy Shield Framework are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission.

 **Privacy** **Shield** **and Data Protection Contact**. Your Privacy Shield and Data Protection Contact for the personal data that we process in connection with the Site is:

Attn: Chief Privacy Officer  
TeddySoft Ltd.  
91 Bul. Hristo Botev Street.  
Plovdiv, 4000, Bulgaria  

Please include sufficient information so we can understand and respond to your specific question.

Back to top

* * *

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information and privacy practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a notice on the Site prior to or simultaneously with the change becoming effective. Your continued use of the Site after any such modification constitutes acceptance of any such modified Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this page periodically for the latest information on our privacy practices. The date of last revision is shown at the top of this Privacy Policy.

Back to top

* * *

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com), or write to:

Attn: Privacy Team  
TeddySoft Ltd.  
91 Bul. Hristo Botev Street.  
Plovdiv, 4000, Bulgaria

Please be sure to include sufficient information so we can understand and respond to your specific question or request.

Back to top

TeddySoft Ltd. and its affiliates (“ **StreamingVideoProvider** ” or “ **we** ”) want our customers (“ **Customers** ” or  “ **you** ”) to be familiar with how we collect, use, share and store information relating to your use of our services and to end users who view your videos via our services (“ **Viewers** ”).

This StreamingVideoProvider Services Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) describes StreamingVideoProvider’s practices regarding information collected by our online products and services (collectively, “ **StreamingVideoProvider Services** ”). Any use of StreamingVideoProvider Services, including the Video Panel and sign-up pages accessible through the StreamingVideoProvider website (including [www.streamingvideoprovider.com](https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com/)), is covered by this Privacy Policy. Those aspects of the StreamingVideoProvider website that do not form a part of the StreamingVideoProvider Services are covered by the StreamingVideoProvider Website Privacy Policy.

 **We do not have a direct relationship with Viewers.** Information collected from Viewers on Customers’ websites or apps is subject to our Customers’ privacy policies. Viewers who have questions or concerns about information collected when they view a video via StreamingVideoProvider Services, or about the content of any such video, should contact our Customer through the website or app on which such video is available. Viewers who are uncertain about whom to contact may contact us at privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com.

### Contents of this Privacy Policy **:**

  * Information We May Collect
  * How We May Use Information
  * How We May Share Information
  * International Data Transfers
  * Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices
  * Right to Request Information
  * Additional Notice for Certain European Residents
  * Additional Notice for Canadian Residents
  * Privacy Shield Notice
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * How to Contact Us

* * *

###  **Information We May Collect**

 **Information Collected from Viewers**. In connection with our provision of StreamingVideoProvider Services, we may collect certain information about Viewers (Viewers can be our customer's website viewers or our customer's customer's viewers in a scenario when our customer is acting as white-label reseller of StreamingVideoProvider Services). Such information may include personal information, which is information that identifies an individual or relates to identifiable person. Information that may be collected when videos are viewed via StreamingVideoProvider Services includes:

  * Unique IDs such as IP addresses or device ID.
  * Viewer name, address, email address, title and industry or any other custom data our Customer may choose to collect from Viwers. Note that StreamingVideoProvider collects this information about Viewers only if a Customer elects to use certain features of StreamingVideoProvider Services (such as Audience Forms, External Uploaders with Metadata forms, Pay-Per-View) that are intended to collect such information.
  * System information, such as device, browser and operating system type and version, screen resolution and preferred language.
  * Referring domain, destination domain and destination path.
  * Video-viewing activity, such as player loads, number of views, viewed minutes, percent of content viewed, new Viewers, unique Viewers, attention span, top domains, geography, traffic sources, search terms and other similar information. This information is aggregated and anonymized (meaning it is not connected to an individual Viewer).
  * Geolocation data.
  * Other personal information of a natural person that may be included in videos or other data that is uploaded to StreamingVideoProvider Services.

 **Information Collected from Customers.   **To enable us to effectively provide StreamingVideoProvider Services, we may collect the following information from individuals authorized by Customers (such as a Customer’s employees) to use StreamingVideoProvider Services:

  * Name, business email address, business telephone number, company, title and business billing address and payment information.
  * Login credentials.

 **Information Collected from Customer’s Customers.   **To enable us to effectively provide white-label StreamingVideoProvider Services, we may collect the following information from customers who are customers of our Customers when using StreamingVideoProvider Services:

  * Name, business email address, business telephone number, company, title and business billing address and payment information.
  * Login credentials.
  * Communication preferences.
  * Unique IDs such as IP address and device IDs.
  * Geolocation data.
  * Other personal information of a natural person that may be included in videos or other data that is uploaded to StreamingVideoProvider Services.

Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technologies. We, and our third-party service providers, may use technologies such as cookies and beacons to quantify use, analyze viewing and engagement with videos displayed using StreamingVideoProvider Services, conduct benchmarking, generate metrics, report to Customers and assess the quality of StreamingVideoProvider Services.

 **Cookies**. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We may link the information we store in cookies to any personal information we obtain from your use of StreamingVideoProvider Services. StreamingVideoProvider Services may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions of StreamingVideoProvider Services.

 **Web Beacons**. We may also use web beacons, tags and scripts in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services. Web beacons, also known as clear GIFs or single-pixel GIFs, are small image files that StreamingVideoProvider Services use to communicate analytics data on Viewer activity and service usage. Alongside cookies, web beacons allow us to accurately count the number of unique Viewers who have viewed a video and activity during a viewing session. This information enables us to measure the performance of our Customer’s videos and allows Customers to evaluate Viewer interaction with their video content.

 **HTTP Headers.   **HTTP headers are information that is transmitted whenever a webpage is viewed, and contain technical information required for communication between a browsing device and a website server. Other electronic communication protocols (such as those used for email) also use headers to transmit information. Information may be transmitted through HTTP (or other electronic communication protocol) headers to StreamingVideoProvider from the Customer’s use of StreamingVideoProvider Services or from Viewer interaction with a Customer's video. This may include information about the device browser, the requested webpage and the computer or device being used (such as a carrier or device identifier).

 **Log Files**. As is true of most online services, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Viewer IP address, browser type, device type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or clickstream data. An IP address is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a Customer uses StreamingVideoProvider Services or a Viewer watches a video, along with the time(s) of the visit(s) and the page(s) visited. We may combine this automatically-collected log information with other information we collect. We do this to provide analytics data to our Customers, to improve the functionality of StreamingVideoProvider Services and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Analytics**. We may use third party analytics services, such as Google Analytics, to track the use of StreamingVideoProvider Services by our Customers. For information on how Google collects and processes information and how to opt out from Google’s collection of your information, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

 **Do Not Track**. StreamingVideoProvider Services do not recognize if a browser sends a “do not track” signal or similar mechanism to indicate the user does not wish to be tracked or receive interest-based ads.

 **Security.   **The security of personal information that StreamingVideoProvider collects while operating the StreamingVideoProvider Service is of great importance to StreamingVideoProvider. We use organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect personal information under our control. No data transmission over the Internet or data storage system, however, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com.

Back to top

* * *

### How We May Use Information

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may use information about our Customers and Viewers for the following purposes or in the following ways:

  * To deliver StreamingVideoProvider Services.
  * To provide our Customers with analytical data and reports about video viewing activity.
  * To provide Customer support.

  * To enable Viewers to register with our Customers in order to be able to watch video content on our Customers’ websites or apps. StreamingVideoProvider collects this information at the direction of the Customer.
  * To personalize StreamingVideoProvider Services.
  * For internal business purposes, such as data analysis, benchmarking, audits, developing new products, enhancing StreamingVideoProvider Services, facilitating product, software and applications development, conducting research, analysis, studies or surveys and identifying usage trends.
  * To protect the security and integrity of StreamingVideoProvider Services, our Customers’ video content and data and our business.
  * To meet our contractual requirements, to comply with applicable legal or regulatory requirements and our policies and to protect against criminal activity, claims and other liabilities.

  * We may also use information about our Customers: to send Customers information and updates regarding StreamingVideoProvider Services, programs and promotions; to fulfil Customer requests, such as to create StreamingVideoProvider Services accounts; or complete Customer purchases.
  * In other ways with appropriate consent.

Back to top

* * *

### How We May Share Information

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may share, disclose and transfer information, including personal information as follows:

  * With the Customer, as part of the StreamingVideoProvider Services.
  * With third-party service providers we use to support StreamingVideoProvider Services and our business. These parties include third parties providing us with services such as website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, analytics and email delivery services. These third parties are authorized to use information related to you only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * With third parties where the Viewer or Customer has requested to use a third-party service (including applications) in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services and has requested that we provide information to such third parties.
  * With our current affiliates and any future corporate subsidiaries or affiliates.
  * With a buyer, investor, new affiliate or other third party in the event that StreamingVideoProvider, or any portion, group or business unit thereof, undergoes a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition, or during steps in contemplation of such activities (e.g., negotiations and due diligence). You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, change in use of your personal information and choices you may have regarding any change in use of your personal information.
  * With third parties for marketing, advertising, promotions, contests or other similar purposes. If required by applicable law, we will share such data for advertising and marketing purposes only in an aggregate, anonymous and de-identified manner.
  * As we believe necessary: under applicable law, including laws outside the Viewer’s or Customer’s country of residence; to comply with any law or directive, judicial or administrative order, legal process or investigation, warrant, subpoena, law enforcement or national security investigation, or as otherwise required or authorized by law; to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside the country of residence; to enforce our policies, terms and conditions; to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates, customers, partners, agents or others; to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property and/or that of our affiliates, customers, partners, agents and any other person or organization; and/or to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

 **Payment Processing.**  We use third-party payment service(s) (“ **Payment Service”** ) to process credit card payments for certain editions of StreamingVideoProvider Services. Customers acknowledge and agree within their StreamingVideoProvider Services agreement that when prompted to provide credit card information, that information gets transmitted directly to the Payment Service. StreamingVideoProvider does not have access to full credit card numbers and does not store such information in its own systems. Information transmitted to the Payment Service is encrypted using SSL technology. The Payment Service is required to comply with all applicable privacy and security laws and the rules and regulations issued by the payment card industry and the credit card companies. Please contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com) if you would like StreamingVideoProvider to facilitate the correction or deletion of your personal information with the Payment Service.

 **Cross-** **Device Tracking**. When Customers or Viewers use devices to display and/or view a Customer’s video content, we may receive information about their devices, including a unique identifier for each device. We and our service providers and third parties we collaborate with, including ad networks, may use cross-device/cross-context tracking. For example, a Viewer might use multiple browsers on a single device, or use various devices (such as desktops, smartphones and tablets), which can result in the individual having multiple accounts or profiles across these various contexts and devices. Cross-device/cross-context technology may be used to connect these various accounts or profiles and the corresponding data from the different contexts and devices.  

 **Aggregate Information.** To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may use, process, transfer and store any data about Viewers and Customers in an anonymous (or pseudonymous) and aggregated manner. We may combine personal information with other information, collected online and offline, including information from third-party sources. We may also use information in other ways with consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. By using StreamingVideoProvider Services, our Customers agree that we may collect, use, share and store anonymized (or pseudonymized) aggregated data collected through StreamingVideoProvider Services for benchmarking, analytics, metrics, research, reporting, machine learning and other legitimate business purposes.

 **Automated Decisions.** To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may collect data in an automated manner and make automated decisions, including using machine-learning algorithms, about Viewers and Customers in order to provide and/or optimize StreamingVideoProvider Services, for security or analytics purposes and for any other lawful purpose.

Back to top

* * *

### International Data Transfers

StreamingVideoProvider Services may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world, including the United States and other countries. Therefore, personal information about Viewers and Customers may be transferred, processed and stored outside the country where StreamingVideoProvider Services are accessed or performed, including to countries where the level of data protection may not be deemed adequate by the local legal or regulatory authority in the country of origin of the data. We will protect the privacy and security of personal information we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy, regardless of where it is processed or stored.

 **European Residents.**   If you are a resident of the European Union (“ **EU** ”), the European Economic Area or Switzerland, please see our Additional Notice for Certain European Residents and our Privacy Shield Notice below.

Back to top

* * *

### Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices

 **Opt-Out.** If you no longer wish to receive marketing-related communications from us, you may opt out by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the latest such message received or by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). Customers may not opt out of certain communications, such as those necessary to keep Customers aware of StreamingVideoProvider Service status and service issues.

 **Retention Period.** To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may retain information for as long as the account of the Customer for whom we collected the information is active, or as long as is reasonably necessary to provide StreamingVideoProvider Services, or as needed for other lawful purposes. We may retain cached or archived copies of information. We may retain anonymized or pseudonymized aggregated data indefinitely, to the extent permitted under applicable law. We also will retain information as long as reasonably necessary to comply with our contractual and/or legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

 **Accuracy of Information.** Accuracy of data is very important to us. Customers should ensure that any information provided to us is up-to-date and Customers may correct information by either logging into their Customer account or by contacting StreamingVideoProvider’s customer support team. In certain situations, Customers may need assistance from customer support in making a change. We will respond to requests to make changes to Customer records as soon as reasonably practicable. We may require Customer representatives to prove their identity before granting access to, or agreeing to update, correct or delete personal information belonging to Customers.

You may request access to, or correction or deletion of personal information, by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com). We will attempt to answer all requests that we correct inaccurate personal information or delete personal information, unless we are required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes.

 **Use of StreamingVideoProvider Services by Children.**   We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy and safety of children. StreamingVideoProvider Services are not intended for use by children under 13 years of age (who reside in the United States) or for children under 16 years of age (who reside in the EU, European Economic Area or Switzerland), although StreamingVideoProvider recognizes that certain of our Customers’ target audiences may be children. Viewers should visit the privacy policy of our Customer to understand how our Customer addresses child-directed video content.

Back to top

* * *

### Right to Request Information

You may request, and we will provide you with, information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may request access to, or correction or deletion of your personal information by contacting us at privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

Back to top

* * *

### Additional Notice for Certain European Residents.

 **The following European Privacy Policy applies to residents of the European Union, the European Economic Area and Switzerland who use StreamingVideoProvider Services.**

 **Personal Data and Processing.** For the purposes of this European Privacy Policy:

“ ** _Personal Data_** ” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of such natural person.

“ ** _Processing_** ” means any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

 **Purposes and Legal Bases for Processing Personal Data**. StreamingVideoProvider Processes data for the purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy, including to provide StreamingVideoProvider Services. To fulfill these purposes, StreamingVideoProvider may access data, including Personal Data, to provide StreamingVideoProvider Services, to correct and address technical or service problems, or in response to contractual requirements. Please see the Information We May Collect, How We May Use Information and How We May Share Information sections for additional details on how we collect, use, disclose and share data, make automated decisions and retain data, including Personal Data, about Viewers and Customers.

Our lawful bases for the Processing of Personal Data are: (i) consent and/or (ii) any other applicable legal bases, such as our legitimate interest in engaging in commerce, offering products and services of value to the customers of StreamingVideoProvider Services, preventing fraud, ensuring information and network security, direct marketing and advertising and complying with industry practices.

 **Additional Rights for European Residents**. As a resident of the EU or a country following substantially-similar legislation regarding the protection of personal data, you may have one or more of the following additional rights available to you:

  *  **Access**. To request a copy of the Personal Data we have collected about you by contacting us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).
  *  **Rectification & Erasure**. To request that we rectify or delete any of the Personal Data about you that is incomplete, incorrect, unnecessary or outdated.
  *  **Objection**. To object, at any time, to Personal Data about you being Processed for direct marketing purposes.
  *  **Restriction of Processing**. To request restriction of Processing of Personal Data about you for certain reasons, such as, for example, if you consider Personal Data about you collected by us to be inaccurate or you have objected to the Processing pending the verification of whether our legitimate grounds for Processing override yours.
  *  **Data Portability**. To request and receive the Personal Data we have collected about you in a commonly used and machine-readable form.
  *  **Right to Withdraw Consent**. If Personal Data about you is processed solely based on your consent and not for any other legitimate interest, to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of our Processing based on such consent before it was withdrawn, including Processing related to existing contracts for our products and services.
  *  **Right to Lodge a Complaint with a DPA**. If you believe our Processing of Personal Data about you is inconsistent with the applicable data protection laws, to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory data protection authority (“DPA”).

To exercise any of the above-listed rights (with the exception of the right to lodge a complaint with a DPA, which you may do directly to a DPA), please contact us at privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com. We will process any requests in accordance with applicable law and within a reasonable period of time. We may need to verify your identity before processing your request. Certain information may be reviewed, corrected and updated by logging into your StreamingVideoProvider Service account and editing the profile information.

If StreamingVideoProvider receives a request from a Viewer, we may refer the request to the Customer and support the Customer in responding to the request.

Compelled Disclosures. StreamingVideoProvider may be required to disclose Personal Data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including disclosures necessary to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or pursuant to judicial orders.

Back to top

* * *

### Additional Notice for Canadian Residents

Canadian residents may have additional rights under Canadian law. Please see the information provided by the [Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada](https://www.priv.gc.ca/en/about-the-opc/publications/guide_ind/) for additional details.

You, and we, confirm that it is our wish that this Privacy Policy and all other related policies be drawn up in English. _Vous reconnaissent avoir exigé la rédaction en anglais du présent document ainsi que tous les documents qui s'y rattachent._

Back to top

* * *

### Privacy Shield Notice

 **EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Notice.**  We have certified our compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield (collectively, the “ **Privacy Shield Framework** ”) with respect to the Personal Data of users of StreamingVideoProvider Services who are residents of the European Union (“ **EU** ”), European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”) and Switzerland that we receive and process through StreamingVideoProvider Services. We certify that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement (hereinafter, “ **Privacy Shield Principles** ”) for personal data of Viewers and Customers in participating European countries. We are responsible for the processing of personal data we receive under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfer to a third party agent, and may be liable for onward transfers in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles. Our certification is available [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list). We may also process Personal Data relating to individuals in Europe via other compliance mechanisms, including use of the European Union Standard Contractual Clauses. 

 **Questions and Complaints**.  If you are a resident of a country participating in the Privacy Shield Framework, you may direct any questions or complaints concerning our Privacy Shield compliance to our Privacy Shield and Data Protection Contact listed below.  We will work with you to resolve your issue.  

If you have not received timely response to your concern relating to data processed under the Privacy Shield Framework, or we have not addressed your concern satisfactorily, you may contact our U.S.-based dispute resolution provider, at no cost to you, at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. If neither StreamingVideoProvider nor our independent dispute resolution provider resolves your complaint, you may use the right to invoke binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel.  However, prior to initiating such arbitration, a resident of a country participating in the Privacy Shield Framework must first: (1) contact us and afford us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2) seek assistance from our designated independent dispute resolution provider and (3) contact the U.S. Department of Commerce (either directly or through a European DPA) and afford the Department of Commerce time to attempt to resolve the issue. If such a resident invokes binding arbitration, each party shall be responsible for its own attorney’s fees. Pursuant to the Privacy Shield, the arbitrator(s) may only impose individual-specific, non-monetary, equitable relief necessary to remedy any violation of the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to the resident.

 **U.S. Federal Trade Commission Enforcement**.  StreamingVideoProvider’s commitments under the Privacy Shield Framework are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission.

 **Privacy** **Shield** **and Data Protection Contact**. Your Privacy Shield and Data Protection Contact for the Personal Data that we Process in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services is:

Attn: Chief Privacy Officer  
TeddySoft Ltd.  
91 Bul. Hristo Botev Street.  
Plovdiv, 4000, Bulgaria  

Please include sufficient information so we can understand and respond to your specific question.

Back to top

* * *

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information and privacy practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a notice on the Site prior to or simultaneously with the change becoming effective. Your continued use of the StreamingVideoProvider Services after any such modification constitutes acceptance of any such modified Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this page periodically for the latest information on our privacy practices. The date of last revision is shown at the top of this Privacy Policy.

Back to top

* * *

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com), or write to:

Attn: Privacy Team  
TeddySoft Ltd.  
91 Bul. Hristo Botev Street.  
Plovdiv, 4000, Bulgaria

Back to top

TeddySoft Ltd. and its affiliates (“ **StreamingVideoProvider** ” or “ **we** ”) want you to be familiar with the types of cookies used on our websites, how we use information collected through cookies, and the choices you have regarding cookies. This Cookies Policy (“ **Cookies Policy** ”) describes our practices with respect to cookies used on our website located at [https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com//](https://www.streamingvideoprovider.com/) and other StreamingVideoProvider websites where this Cookies Policy is made available (“collectively, the “ **Site** ”).

This Cookies Policy does not address cookies that may be used by services offered by StreamingVideoProvider (the “ **StreamingVideoProvider Services** ”), including those aspects of StreamingVideoProvider Services that are accessible via this Site, including the Video Panel, support pages, and documentation. For more information about cookies used within StreamingVideoProvider Services, please see our StreamingVideoProvider Services Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Cookies Policy, or our privacy practices generally, please contact us at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com).

### Contents of the Cookies Policy:

  * What Are Cookies?
  * Does the Site Use Cookies?
  * Types of Cookies Used on the Site
  * How to Disable Cookies
  * Changes to this Cookies Policy
  * How to Contact Us

* * *

### What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer or other device. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that deployed the cookie on your computer or other device. Cookies are used for various purposes, as described in Types of Cookies Used on the Site below. We may link the information we store in cookies to personal information you submit while on our Site. We may receive reports from our third-party service providers about the use of cookies deployed by such third-party service providers on an individual and/or aggregated basis. To learn more about cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> or [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

Back to top

* * *

### Does the Site Use Cookies?

Yes. StreamingVideoProvider and our third-party service providers use cookies and other technologies to enhance user experience on the Site.

Back to top

* * *

### Types of Cookies Used on the Site

The Site uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies to help remember use preferences and improve the user experience. Cookies that we may use could also be grouped into the following categories (and may include persistent or session cookies depending on the context):

  *  **Analytics/Performance cookies** that collect information about how you use our Site. These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of unique users visiting the Site (and Site features) and to see how users move around our website. This helps us to improve the way our website works. These cookies are sometimes placed by third-party providers of web traffic analysis services. These cookies may be either persistent or session cookies.

  *  **Functionality cookies** that remember choices you make and recognize you when you return. These cookies enable us to personalize our content, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region). These cookies are generally persistent cookies.

  *  **Ad Functionality cookies** that are functionality cookies for the purposes of advertising. These cookies are generally persistent cookies.

  *  **Targeting cookies** that collect information about your browsing habits such as the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We use this information to make our website more relevant to your interests, and, if we enable advertising, to make advertising more relevant to you, as well as to limit the number of times you see a particular ad. These cookies are usually placed by third-party advertising networks. These cookies may track you across websites that you visit and this information is shared with third-party organizations like advertisers. These cookies are generally persistent cookies.

  *  **Retargeting cookies** are essentially a form of targeting cookies that enable advertising based on your browsing habits and the links you have followed. These cookies are generally persistent cookies.

Back to top

* * *

### How to Disable Cookies

It is possible to adjust your web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is deployed your computer, to block cookies altogether or to activate or later de-activate cookies once deployed to your computer.

To learn more about how to control cookie settings through your browser:

  * Click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) to learn more about “Private Browsing” and managing cookie settings in Firefox;
  * Click [here](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647) to learn more about “Incognito” and managing cookie settings in Chrome;
  * Click [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies) to learn more about “InPrivate” and managing cookie settings in Internet Explorer; or
  * Click [here](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US) to learn more about “Private Browsing” and managing cookie settings in Safari.

If you do not want session ID cookies to collect information about your Site visit, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://d.company-target.com/opt-out). You may remove persistent cookies by following directions provided by your Internet browser at the links above. While we do not require you to use cookies, certain parts of the Site will not function properly if you set your browser to refuse cookies.

Back to top

* * *

### Changes to this Cookies Policy

We may update this Cookies Policy to reflect changes to our information and cookies practices by posting an updated version of this Cookies Policy on this page, or with any notice to you if required by applicable law. Your continued use of the Site after any such update constitutes acceptance of any such modified Cookies Policy. We encourage you to review this page periodically for the latest information on our cookies practices. The date of last revision is shown at the top of this Cookies Policy.

Back to top

* * *

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Cookies Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com](mailto:privacy@streamingvideoprovider.com), or write to:

Attn: Privacy Team  
TeddySoft Ltd.  
91 Bul. Hristo Botev Street.  
Plovdiv, 4000, Bulgaria

Please be sure to include sufficient information so we can understand and respond to your specific question or request.

Back to top

All terms used herein are as defined in the Data Processing Addendum and/or Service Agreement entered into between StreamingVideoProvider and Company.

StreamingVideoProvider engages with certain third-party Subprocessors to provide specific functionality in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services. These Subprocessors are set forth below and have access to and may Process certain service data, which may include Personal Data, in order to provide the identified StreamingVideoProvider Services.

This list will be updated from time to time to reflect the then-current Subprocessors being used in connection with StreamingVideoProvider Services and notice will be provided as set forth in the Company’s Data Processing Addendum. 

 **Vendor**

| 

 **Description of Services**

| 

 **Entity Location(s)**  
  
---|---|---  
  
 **CDN Providers**  
  
CDN77

| 

Content delivery services for static content ( images, js, html,css )

| 

Global  
  
 **Cloud Storage**  
  
Google

| 

Storage of Content and analytics data

| 

Global  
  
 **Data Centers**  
  
EvoSwitch

iomart

SoftLayer Dutch Holdings BV

DigitalOcean

Vultr

| 

Data center services

| 

Netherlands

United Kingdom

Netherlands

USA

USA  
  
 **Other Providers**  
  
Google Analytics

| 

User activity tracking

| 

Global  
  
FullStory

| 

Analytics & Mouse Movement Tracking

| 

USA  
  
Intercom

| 

Customer Relationship Manager

| 

USA  
  
Sentry.io

| 

Application error tracking and monitoring

| 

USA  
  
Status.io

| 

System Status communications

| 

USA
